<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="sign_in">SIGN IN</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account_sign_up">Already Have an Account? Sign Up</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="enter_username">Enter Username</string>
    <string name="name1">Name</string>
    <string name="enter_username1">Enter Username</string>
    <string name="enter_password">Enter Password</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account_sign_in">Already Have an Account? Sign In</string>
    <string name="sign_up_for_a_new_account">Sign Up for a New Account</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="enter_name">Enter Name</string>
    <string name="enter_email">Enter Email</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="notification_fragment">Notification Fragment</string>
    <string name="profile_fragment">Profile Fragment</string>
    <string name="home_fragment">Home Fragment</string>
    <string name="chat_fragment">Chat Fragment</string>
    <string name="don_t_have_an_account_sign_up">Don\'t_have_an_account_sign_up</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="todo1">TODO</string>
    <string name="todo2">TODO</string>
    <string name="todo3">TODO</string>
    <string name="home1">Home</string>
    <string name="interests">Interests</string>
    <string name="science">Science</string>
    <string name="sports">Sports</string>
    <string name="journalism">Journalism</string>
    <string name="automobile">Automobile</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="environment">Environment</string>
    <string name="politics">Politics</string>
    <string name="philosophy">Philosophy</string>
    <string name="biology">Biology</string>
    <string name="current_affairs">Current Affairs</string>
    <string name="tests">Tests</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="home2">Home</string>
    <string name="science1">Science</string>
    <string name="physical_education">Physical Education</string>
    <string name="arts">Arts</string>
    <string name="commerce">Commerce</string>
    <string name="technology">Technology</string>
    <string name="current_affairs1">Current Affairs</string>
    <string name="tests1">Tests</string>
    <string name="share1">Share</string>
    <string name="feedback1">Feedback</string>
    <string name="edura">EDURA</string>
    <string name="annuuu">\@annuuu</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_tutorial">Navigation Drawer Tutorial</string>
    <string name="todo11">TODO</string>
    <string name="federick_johan">Federick Johan</string>
    <string name="federick_johans_gmail_com">federick_johans@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="todo12">TODO</string>
    <string name="todo13">TODO</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="todo14">TODO</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="todo15">TODO</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log Out</string>
    <string name="gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="status">Status</string>
    <string name="student">Student</string>
    <string name="dob">DOB</string>
    <string name="_25_07_2022">25-07-2022</string>
    <string name="qualification">Qualification</string>
    <string name="state">State</string>
    <string name="mca">MCA</string>
    <string name="new_delhi">New Delhi</string>
    <string name="home11">Home</string>
    <string name="todo21">TODO</string>
    <string name="others">Others</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="enter_your_name">Enter your name</string>


    <string name="zinnias">How to Plant, Grow, and Care for Zinnia Flowers</string>
    <string name="description_zinnias">Zinnias are easy to grow annual flowers that come in a wide variety of colors and sizes. Here are the steps to plant, grow, and care for zinnias:\n\n
<br><b>1. Choose a sunny spot:</b> Zinnias require at least six hours of direct sunlight per day, so choose a spot in your garden that gets plenty of sun.\n\n</br>
<br><b>2. Prepare the soil:</b> Zinnias prefer well-draining soil that is rich in organic matter. Add compost or well-rotted manure to your soil before planting to improve its texture and fertility.\n\n</br>
<br><b>3. Plant the seeds:</b> Zinnias can be grown from seeds, which should be planted in the spring after the last frost. Sow the seeds directly into the soil, spacing them 6-18 inches apart depending on the size of the zinnia variety. Cover the seeds with a light layer of soil and water gently.\n\n</br>
<br><b>4. Water regularly:</b> Keep the soil moist but not waterlogged, especially during hot and dry periods. Zinnias are drought-tolerant, but they will produce more flowers if they are watered regularly.\n\n</br>
<br><b>5. Fertilize occasionally:</b> Zinnias are light feeders and do not require heavy fertilization. You can add a balanced fertilizer to the soil once or twice during the growing season to provide the plants with the nutrients they need.\n\n</br>
<br><b>6. Deadhead spent blooms:</b> Zinnias will continue to produce new flowers if you deadhead (remove) the spent blooms regularly. Use scissors or garden shears to cut the stem just above the first set of leaves.\n\n</br>
<br><b>7. Control pests and diseases:</b> Zinnias are relatively pest and disease-free, but they can be affected by powdery mildew, aphids, and spider mites. If you notice any signs of pests or diseases, treat them promptly with organic or chemical pesticides.\n\n</br>
By following these steps, you can plant, grow, and care for beautiful zinnia flowers that will brighten up your garden all summer long.
    </string>

    <string name="bee">Creating and Managing a Bee Garden</string>
    <string name="description_bee">Creating and managing a bee garden can be a fun and rewarding experience. Here are some steps to get you started:\n\n
<br><b>1. Choose a location:</b> Choose a spot in your yard or garden that gets plenty of sunlight and is protected from strong winds. Ideally, the location should also be close to a source of water, such as a pond or stream.\n\n</br>
<br><b>2. Select the right plants:</b> Choose plants that provide a good source of nectar and pollen for bees. Native wildflowers, herbs, and flowering trees are good choices. Make sure to plant a variety of flowers that bloom at different times throughout the growing season to provide a consistent food source for bees.\n\n</br>
<br><b>3. Provide nesting sites:</b> Bees need a place to lay their eggs and raise their young. You can provide nesting sites by installing bee boxes or providing areas with bare, sandy soil.\n\n</br>
<br><b>4. Avoid pesticides:</b> Bees are sensitive to pesticides and other chemicals. Avoid using pesticides and herbicides in your garden, and opt for organic methods of pest control instead.\n\n</br>
<br><b>5. Maintain your garden:</b> Keep your bee garden healthy and thriving by watering it regularly, removing weeds, and pruning plants as needed.\n\n</br>
<br><b>6. Learn about bees:</b> Educate yourself about the types of bees in your area and their needs. Understanding the behavior of bees can help you create a garden that is attractive to them and supports their health and well-being.\n\n</br>
By following these steps, you can create a bee garden that provides a safe and healthy habitat for bees while also enjoying the beauty of flowering plants in your garden.
    </string>

    <string name="agave">How to Plant, Grow, and Care for Agave Plants</string>
    <string name="description_agave">Agave plants are a type of succulent that are known for their striking appearance and drought tolerance. They can be grown both indoors and outdoors and are relatively low-maintenance. Here are some steps to plant, grow, and care for Agave plants:\n\n
<br><b>1. Choose a suitable location:</b> Agave plants prefer well-draining soil and lots of sunlight. Choose a location that gets at least six hours of direct sunlight each day.\n\n</br>
<br><b>2. Plant the Agave:</b> Dig a hole that is slightly larger than the root ball of the Agave plant. Place the plant in the hole and backfill with soil. Make sure to leave some space around the plant to allow for growth.\n\n</br>
<br><b>3. Water the Agave:</b> Water the Agave plant deeply after planting. After that, water the plant sparingly, allowing the soil to dry out between waterings. Overwatering can cause root rot.\n\n</br>
<br><b>4. Fertilize the Agave:</b> Agave plants do not require much fertilizer. However, you can use a slow-release fertilizer in the spring and summer to encourage growth.\n\n</br>
<br><b>5. Prune the Agave:</b> Remove any dead or damaged leaves from the Agave plant. This will improve its appearance and help prevent disease.\n\n</br>
<br><b>6. Protect the Agave:</b> If you live in a cold climate, protect the Agave plant from frost by covering it with a blanket or moving it indoors.\n\n</br>
<br><b>7. Propagate the Agave:</b> Agave plants can be propagated by removing offsets or pups that grow from the base of the plant. These can be replanted in their own pots or in the garden.\n\n</br>
Overall, Agave plants are relatively low-maintenance and can add a unique and striking element to any garden or indoor space.
    </string>

    <string name="broccoli">How to Plant, Grow, and Care for Broccoli</string>
    <string name="description_broccoli">Broccoli is a nutritious and delicious vegetable that can be grown in the garden or in containers. It requires cool temperatures and consistent moisture to grow properly. Here are some steps to plant, grow, and care for broccoli:\n\n
<br><b>1. Choose a suitable location:</b> Broccoli prefers full sun but can tolerate some shade. It also requires well-draining soil with a pH of 6.0 to 7.5.\n\n</br>
<br><b>2. Plant the Broccoli:</b> Plant broccoli seeds or seedlings in the spring or fall. Seeds should be planted about half an inch deep and 3 inches apart. Seedlings should be planted at the same depth as they were in their container, and spaced 18 to 24 inches apart.\n\n</br>
<br><b>3. Water the Broccoli:</b> Keep the soil consistently moist by watering the plants deeply once or twice a week. Avoid overwatering, which can lead to fungal diseases.\n\n</br>
<br><b>4. Fertilize the Broccoli:</b> Broccoli plants benefit from a balanced fertilizer every 3-4 weeks. Alternatively, you can add compost to the soil before planting to provide nutrients.\n\n</br>
<br><b>5. Mulch the Broccoli:</b> Cover the soil around the broccoli plants with a layer of mulch to retain moisture and suppress weeds.\n\n</br>
<br><b>6. Protect the Broccoli:</b> Cover the broccoli plants with netting or row covers to protect them from pests like cabbage worms and aphids. You can also use organic insecticides if necessary.\n\n</br>
<br><b>7. Harvest the Broccoli:</b> Harvest the broccoli heads when they are firm and tight, before the flowers start to bloom. Cut the heads off with a sharp knife, leaving a few inches of stem attached to the plant. This will encourage the plant to produce side shoots, which can be harvested later.\n\n</br>
By following these steps, you can enjoy a bountiful harvest of nutritious broccoli from your garden or containers.
    </string>

    <string name="butterfly">Creating and Managing a Butterfly Garden</string>
    <string name="description_butterfly">Creating a butterfly garden is a beautiful way to attract and support local butterfly populations. Here are some steps to create and manage a butterfly garden:\n\n
<br><b>1. Choose a sunny location:</b> Butterflies need sunshine to stay active, so choose a location that receives at least 6 hours of sunlight each day.\n\n</br>
<br><b>2. Select host plants:</b> Butterflies lay their eggs on specific plants, which serve as food sources for the emerging caterpillars. Research which host plants are native to your area and incorporate them into your garden.\n\n</br>
<br><b>3. Choose nectar plants:</b> Butterflies also need nectar plants for food. Select a variety of flowering plants that bloom at different times throughout the season to provide a constant source of nectar.\n\n</br>
<br><b>4. Provide a water source:</b> Butterflies need water to drink and bathe. Provide a shallow dish of water or a birdbath with pebbles for them to perch on.\n\n</br>
<br><b>5. Add shelter:</b> Butterflies need shelter to rest during hot or windy weather. Plant shrubs or small trees for them to hide in.\n\n</br>
<br><b>6. Avoid pesticides:</b> Pesticides can harm butterflies and their larvae. Use organic methods to manage pests in your garden.\n\n</br>
<br><b>7. Maintain the garden:</b> Keep the garden weeded and watered, and deadhead spent flowers to encourage new growth. Remove any diseased or damaged plants promptly to prevent the spread of disease.\n\n</br>
<br><b>8. Observe and enjoy:</b> Spend time in your garden observing the butterflies and their behaviors. Keep a journal or take photos to track which species visit your garden.\n\n</br>
By following these steps, you can create a beautiful and thriving butterfly garden that supports local butterfly populations.
    </string>


    <string name="coleus">How to Plant, Grow, and Care for Coleus</string>
    <string name="description_coleus">Coleus is a popular foliage plant that comes in a wide variety of colors and patterns. It is easy to grow and can be grown both indoors and outdoors. Here are some steps to plant, grow, and care for Coleus:\n\n
<br><b>1. Choose a suitable location:</b> Coleus plants prefer partial shade to full shade. Choose a location that gets 3-4 hours of direct sunlight each day, or bright indirect light if growing indoors.\n\n</br>
<br><b>2. Plant the Coleus:</b> Plant Coleus seeds or cuttings in well-draining soil. If starting from seeds, plant them about 1/8 inch deep. If starting from cuttings, dip the cut end in rooting hormone and plant it in a pot or in the ground.\n\n</br>
<br><b>3. Water the Coleus:</b> Keep the soil consistently moist by watering the plants deeply once or twice a week. Avoid overwatering, which can lead to root rot.\n\n</br>
<br><b>4. Fertilize the Coleus:</b> Coleus plants benefit from a balanced fertilizer every 4-6 weeks during the growing season. Alternatively, you can add compost to the soil before planting to provide nutrients.\n\n</br>
<br><b>5. Pinch back the Coleus:</b> To encourage bushy growth, pinch back the tips of the Coleus plant as it grows. This will also prevent it from becoming too leggy.\n\n</br>
<br><b>6. Protect the Coleus:</b> Coleus plants can be damaged by frost, so bring them indoors or cover them with a blanket or tarp during cold weather.\n\n</br>
<br><b>7. Propagate the Coleus:</b> Coleus plants can be propagated by taking stem cuttings and rooting them in water or soil. Once rooted, the cuttings can be planted in their own pots or in the garden.\n\n</br>
By following these steps, you can enjoy a beautiful and colorful display of Coleus in your garden or indoor space.
    </string>


        <string name="milkweed">How to Plant, Grow, and Care for Milkweed</string>
    <string name="description_milkweed">Milkweed is a critical plant for the survival of monarch butterflies, as it is the sole food source for monarch caterpillars. Here are some steps to plant, grow, and care for milkweed:\n\n
<br><b>1. Choose a suitable location:</b> Milkweed prefers full sun but can tolerate some shade. It also requires well-draining soil.\n\n</br>
<br><b>2. Plant the Milkweed:</b> Plant milkweed seeds or seedlings in the spring or fall. Seeds should be planted about 1/4 inch deep and 12 to 24 inches apart. Seedlings should be planted at the same depth as they were in their container, and spaced 12 to 24 inches apart.\n\n</br>
<br><b>3. Water the Milkweed:</b> Keep the soil consistently moist by watering the plants deeply once or twice a week. Avoid overwatering, which can lead to fungal diseases.\n\n</br>
<br><b>4. Fertilize the Milkweed:</b> Milkweed plants do not require fertilizer, but they will benefit from a thin layer of compost added to the soil around the plants.\n\n</br>
<br><b>5. Mulch the Milkweed:</b> Cover the soil around the milkweed plants with a layer of mulch to retain moisture and suppress weeds.\n\n</br>
<br><b>6. Protect the Milkweed:</b> Milkweed can be damaged by pests like aphids and milkweed bugs. Use organic insecticides if necessary to manage these pests.\n\n</br>
<br><b>7. Let the Milkweed Stand:</b> Do not cut back the milkweed in the fall, as the dead stems provide winter habitat for insects and birds. Leave the plants standing until early spring, when new growth appears.\n\n</br>
By following these steps, you can help support the survival of monarch butterflies by providing them with a crucial food source.
    </string>


    <string name="mint">How to Plant, Grow, and Care for Mint</string>
    <string name="description_mint">Mint is a fragrant and easy-to-grow herb that can be used for cooking, teas, and other purposes. Here are some steps to plant, grow, and care for mint:\n\n
<br><b>1. Choose a suitable location:</b> Mint prefers a partially shaded area with well-draining soil. It can also tolerate full sun if it is kept well-watered.\n\n</br>
<br><b>2. Plant the Mint:</b> Mint can be propagated from stem cuttings or planted from seed. If planting from seed, plant them about 1/4 inch deep and space them 18 to 24 inches apart. If planting from cuttings, remove the lower leaves and plant the stem about 2 inches deep.\n\n</br>
<br><b>3. Water the Mint:</b> Keep the soil consistently moist by watering the plants deeply once or twice a week. Avoid overwatering, which can lead to root rot.\n\n</br>
<br><b>4. Fertilize the Mint:</b> Mint does not require fertilizer, but it will benefit from a thin layer of compost or organic matter added to the soil around the plants.\n\n</br>
<br><b>5. Pinch back the Mint:</b> To encourage bushy growth, pinch back the tips of the mint plant as it grows. This will also prevent it from becoming too leggy.\n\n</br>
<br><b>6. Protect the Mint:</b> Mint can be damaged by pests like spider mites and aphids. Use organic insecticides if necessary to manage these pests.\n\n</br>
<br><b>7. Harvest the Mint:</b> Harvest the mint leaves as needed by cutting the stems just above a set of leaves. This will encourage the plant to produce new growth.\n\n</br>
By following these steps, you can enjoy a bountiful harvest of fresh and fragrant mint.
    </string>

    <string name="parsley">How to Plant, Grow, and Care for Parsley</string>
    <string name="description_parsley">Parsley is a popular herb used in a wide range of dishes and can be easily grown in a garden or container. Here are some steps to plant, grow, and care for parsley:\n\n
<br><b>1. Choose a suitable location:</b> Parsley prefers partial shade to full sun and well-draining soil.\n\n</br>
<br><b>2. Plant the Parsley:</b> Parsley seeds can take up to 4 weeks to germinate, so it\'s best to soak the seeds overnight before planting them. Plant the seeds about 1/4 inch deep and space them 6 inches apart.\n\n</br>
<br><b>3. Water the Parsley:</b> Parsley prefers consistent moisture, so water the plants deeply once or twice a week, depending on the weather conditions. Be sure not to overwater, as this can lead to root rot.\n\n</br>
<br><b>4. Fertilize the Parsley:</b> Parsley plants benefit from a balanced fertilizer every 4-6 weeks during the growing season. Alternatively, you can add compost to the soil before planting to provide nutrients.\n\n</br>
<br><b>5. Pinch back the Parsley:</b> To encourage bushy growth, pinch back the tips of the parsley plant as it grows. This will also prevent it from becoming too leggy.\n\n</br>
<br><b>6. Protect the Parsley:</b> Parsley can be damaged by pests like aphids and spider mites. Use organic insecticides if necessary to manage these pests.\n\n</br>
<br><b>7. Harvest the Parsley:</b> Harvest the parsley leaves as needed by cutting the stems just above a set of leaves. Be sure to leave at least two sets of leaves on the plant to ensure continued growth.\n\n</br>
By following these steps, you can enjoy a bountiful harvest of fresh parsley for use in your favorite dishes.
    </string>

    <string name="peas">How to Plant, Grow, and Care for Peas</string>
    <string name="description_peas">Peas are a cool-season crop that can be grown in the spring or fall. Here are some steps to plant, grow, and care for peas:\n\n
<br><b>1. Choose a suitable location:</b> Peas prefer full sun and well-draining soil. It\'s best to plant them in a location that gets at least 6 hours of sunlight per day.\n\n</br>
<br><b>2. Plant the Peas:</b> Plant the pea seeds about 1-2 inches deep and 2-3 inches apart. Space the rows about 18-24 inches apart. If you\'re planting in the fall, be sure to do so 6-8 weeks before the first frost.\n\n</br>
<br><b>3. Water the Peas:</b> Keep the soil consistently moist by watering the plants deeply once or twice a week, depending on the weather conditions. Be sure not to overwater, as this can lead to root rot.\n\n</br>
<br><b>4. Fertilize the Peas:</b> Peas do not require fertilizer, but they will benefit from a thin layer of compost or organic matter added to the soil around the plants.\n\n</br>
<br><b>5. Provide Support for the Peas:</b> Peas are climbing plants that require support to grow upright. You can use trellises, stakes, or a fence to provide support for the plants.\n\n</br>
<br><b>6. Protect the Peas:</b> Peas can be damaged by pests like aphids and pea weevils. Use organic insecticides if necessary to manage these pests.\n\n</br>
<br><b>7. Harvest the Peas:</b> Harvest the pea pods when they are plump and have a bright green color. Be sure to pick them frequently to encourage continued production.\n\n</br>
By following these steps, you can enjoy a bountiful harvest of fresh and tasty peas.
    </string>

    <string name="rock">Creating and Managing a Rock Garden</string>
    <string name="description_rock">A rock garden is a beautiful and low-maintenance way to enhance your outdoor space. Here are some steps to create and manage a rock garden:\n\n
<br><b>1. Choose a suitable location:</b> Rock gardens can be created in a variety of locations, but they generally require good drainage and full sun to partial shade. Choose an area that receives at least 6 hours of sunlight per day.\n\n</br>
<br><b>2. Plan the Rock Garden:</b> Sketch out a design for your rock garden on paper before beginning. Consider the size and placement of rocks, as well as any plants or other features you want to include.\n\n</br>
<br><b>3. Prepare the Site:</b> Remove any existing vegetation and weeds from the site. Use a tiller or garden fork to loosen the soil and mix in compost or other organic matter to improve drainage.\n\n</br>
<br><b>4. Place the Rocks:</b> Place the largest rocks first, using them to create a natural-looking arrangement. Arrange the smaller rocks around the larger ones, leaving space for plants to grow in between.\n\n</br>
<br><b>5. Add Soil and Mulch:</b> Add a layer of well-draining soil around the rocks, filling in any gaps. Top with a layer of mulch to help retain moisture and suppress weeds.\n\n</br>
<br><b>6. Choose and Plant the Plants:</b> Choose plants that are well-suited to a rock garden, such as succulents, alpine plants, and groundcovers. Plant them in the soil between the rocks, taking care not to disturb the rocks or their placement.\n\n</br>
<br><b>7. Water and Maintain the Rock Garden:</b> Water the plants regularly, keeping the soil consistently moist but not waterlogged. Prune plants as needed to maintain their shape and prevent overcrowding. Weed the garden regularly to keep it looking neat and tidy.\n\n</br>
By following these steps, you can create a beautiful and low-maintenance rock garden that will enhance your outdoor space for years to come.
    </string>


    <string name="tulip">How to Plant, Grow, and Care for Tulip</string>
    <string name="description_tulip">Tulips are a popular spring flower known for their colorful blooms. Here are some steps to plant, grow, and care for tulips:\n\n
<br><b>1. Choose a suitable location:</b> Tulips prefer full sun to partial shade and well-draining soil. Avoid planting them in areas that are prone to standing water or that get too much wind.\n\n</br>
<br><b>2. Plant the Tulips:</b> Plant tulip bulbs in the fall, about 6 to 8 weeks before the ground freezes. Dig a hole that is about 2 to 3 times the height of the bulb and plant the bulb pointy-side up, with the flat side facing down. Space the bulbs about 4 to 6 inches apart.\n\n</br>
<br><b>3. Water the Tulips:</b> Water the tulip bulbs after planting and then periodically throughout the fall if there is a dry spell. In general, tulips do not need a lot of water during their dormant period in the winter.\n\n</br>
<br><b>4. Fertilize the Tulips:</b> Fertilize the tulips in the fall when planting with a bulb fertilizer. Follow the instructions on the fertilizer package for the correct amount to use.\n\n</br>
<br><b>5. Mulch the Tulips:</b> Mulch around the tulip bulbs with a layer of shredded leaves or other organic material to help protect them from extreme temperatures and to retain moisture.\n\n</br>
<br><b>6. Protect the Tulips:</b> Tulips are often eaten by animals such as squirrels, rabbits, and deer. Protect the bulbs by covering the planting area with netting or using repellent sprays.\n\n</br>
<br><b>7. Enjoy the Tulips:</b> In the spring, watch as the tulips emerge from the ground and grow into beautiful flowers. Cut the flowers with a sharp pair of scissors, making a clean cut just above a set of leaves.\n\n</br>
By following these steps, you can grow healthy and beautiful tulips that will brighten up your garden in the spring.
    </string>

    <string name="waterlily">How to Plant, Grow, and Care for Water Lily</string>
    <string name="description_waterlily">Water lilies are beautiful aquatic plants that can add color and interest to your water garden. Here are some steps to plant, grow, and care for water lilies:\n\n
<br><b>1. Choose a suitable location:</b> Water lilies need a still, shallow body of water with at least 6 hours of direct sunlight each day. They can be planted in a pond, a water garden, or a container with at least 5 gallons of water.\n\n</br>
<br><b>2. Plant the Water Lily:</b> Plant the water lily in a planting container filled with a special aquatic planting mix. Gently press the roots into the soil and cover with a layer of pea gravel to prevent the soil from washing away. Lower the container into the water and place it on a shelf at a depth of about 12 to 18 inches.\n\n</br>
<br><b>3. Water the Water Lily:</b> Keep the water level in the container at a consistent level, about 2 inches below the top of the container. Water lilies prefer still water and do not need to be watered.\n\n</br>
<br><b>4. Fertilize the Water Lily:</b> Water lilies benefit from regular fertilization. Use a special aquatic fertilizer formulated for water lilies and follow the instructions on the package for the correct amount to use.\n\n</br>
<br><b>5. Prune the Water Lily:</b> Prune the water lily regularly to remove any yellow or dead leaves and to promote new growth. Cut the leaves at the base of the stem with a sharp pair of scissors.\n\n</br>
<br><b>6. Protect the Water Lily:</b> Protect the water lily from pests like aphids and water snails. Use organic pest control methods if necessary to manage these pests.\n\n</br>
<br><b>7. Enjoy the Water Lily:</b> Watch as the water lily grows and produces beautiful flowers throughout the growing season. Admire the beauty of the plant from a distance to avoid disturbing it.\n\n</br>
By following these steps, you can successfully plant, grow, and care for water lilies and enjoy their beauty in your water garden.
    </string>

    <string name="landfills">How To Reduce Food Waste In Landfills By Composting</string>
    <string name="description_landfills">Composting is a great way to reduce food waste in landfills and turn it into a valuable resource for your garden or plants. Here are some steps to get started with composting:\n\n
<br><b>1. Choose a composting method:</b> There are different ways to compost, including traditional composting bins, worm composting, and open-air composting. Choose the method that works best for your situation.\n\n</br>
<br><b>2. Collect food scraps:</b> Collect food scraps from your kitchen, including fruit and vegetable peels, eggshells, coffee grounds, and tea bags. Avoid adding meat, dairy, or fatty foods, as they can attract pests and take longer to decompose.\n\n</br>
<br><b>3. Add other organic materials:</b> In addition to food scraps, add other organic materials to your compost pile, such as grass clippings, leaves, and yard trimmings. These materials will help create a balanced mix of green and brown materials that will decompose more quickly.\n\n</br>
<br><b>4. Mix and aerate:</b> Mix the materials in your compost pile regularly to promote decomposition and aerate the pile by turning it with a pitchfork or compost aerator.\n\n</br>
<br><b>5. Keep it moist:</b> Keep your compost pile moist, but not too wet. If it is too dry, the materials will not decompose properly. If it is too wet, it can become smelly and attract pests.\n\n</br>
<br><b>6. Harvest the compost:</b> After several months, your compost will be ready to use in your garden or for potted plants. Use a pitchfork to remove the finished compost from the bottom of the pile.\n\n</br>
<br><b>7. Use the compost:</b> Use the finished compost as a natural fertilizer for your garden or potted plants. Mix it into the soil or sprinkle it on top of the soil around your plants.\n\n</br>
By following these steps, you can reduce food waste in landfills and create a valuable resource for your garden or plants.
    </string>

    <string name="yardwaste">Can You Compost Yard Waste – Ways To Compost Garden Waste</string>
    <string name="description_yardwaste">Yes, you can compost yard waste and garden waste to create a valuable resource for your garden or plants. Here are some ways to compost garden waste:\n\n
<br><b>1. Compost pile or bin:</b> You can create a compost pile or bin to compost your garden waste. Use a mix of brown materials, such as dry leaves or straw, and green materials, such as grass clippings or fresh plant trimmings, to create a balanced compost mix. Turn the pile regularly to promote decomposition and keep it moist.\n\n</br>
<br><b>2. Trench composting:</b> Trench composting involves digging a trench in your garden and burying your garden waste in it. Cover the waste with soil and let it decompose naturally over time.\n\n</br>
<br><b>3. Vermicomposting:</b> Vermicomposting uses worms to break down garden waste into nutrient-rich compost. You can purchase a worm bin or create your own using a plastic container. Add your garden waste to the bin along with some bedding material, such as shredded newspaper, and add worms to the bin. Keep the bin moist and well-aerated to promote decomposition.\n\n</br>
<br><b>4. Grasscycling:</b> Grasscycling involves leaving grass clippings on your lawn after mowing. The clippings will decompose and release nutrients back into the soil, reducing the need for fertilizers.\n\n</br>
<br><b>5. Mulching:</b> You can use a mulching mower to chop up leaves and small branches and use them as mulch in your garden. Mulch helps to retain moisture in the soil and suppress weeds while adding nutrients to the soil as it decomposes.\n\n</br>
By composting your garden waste, you can reduce the amount of waste that goes to landfills and create a valuable resource for your garden or plants. Choose the composting method that works best for you and enjoy the benefits of nutrient-rich compost for your garden.
    </string>

    <string name="wormindoor">Worm Farming Guide For Indoor Gardeners</string>
    <string name="description_wormindoor">Worm farming, or vermiculture, is a great way for indoor gardeners to produce nutrient-rich compost for their plants while also reducing their waste. Here\'s a guide on how to get started with worm farming:\n\n
<br><b>1. Choose your worms:</b> The most common worm used for vermiculture is the red wigglers, also known as Eisenia fetida. You can purchase them from a worm supplier or online. Start with about 1 pound of worms for every 2 square feet of worm bin.\n\n</br>
<br><b>2. Choose your container:</b> You can use a plastic bin with a lid or a wooden box for your worm bin. Make sure it has a lid to keep the worms in and pests out. The size of the container will depend on the amount of waste you produce and the number of worms you have.\n\n</br>
<br><b>3. Add bedding material:</b> The bedding material provides a home for the worms and helps to absorb moisture. You can use shredded newspaper, cardboard, or leaves as bedding material. Moisten the bedding material with water so that it is damp but not soaked.\n\n</br>
<br><b>14. Add food scraps:</b> Worms eat a variety of food scraps, including fruit and vegetable scraps, coffee grounds, and tea bags. Avoid adding meat, dairy, or oily foods as they can attract pests and smell bad. Chop up the food scraps into small pieces to help the worms digest them.\n\n</br>
<br><b>5 Maintain the worm bin:</b> Keep the bedding material moist but not too wet, and add food scraps regularly. Avoid overfeeding the worms, as it can lead to bad odors and other issues. When the worm bin is full, remove the finished compost and add fresh bedding material and food scraps.\n\n</br>
<br><b>6. Harvest the compost:</b> After a few months, the worms will have turned the bedding material and food scraps into nutrient-rich compost. You can harvest the compost by removing the top layer of bedding material and taking out the finished compost from the bottom of the bin.\n\n</br>
By following these simple steps, indoor gardeners can produce nutrient-rich compost for their plants while reducing their waste. Worm farming is a fun and easy way to contribute to a sustainable lifestyle and grow healthy plants.
    </string>

    <string name="exfcold">How To Prevent Trees Exploding From Cold This Winter</string>
    <string name="description_exfcold">In extremely cold weather, water inside the cells of trees can freeze and expand, causing the cells to burst and leading to tree damage or even tree explosion. Here are some ways to prevent trees from exploding from the cold this winter:\n\n
<br><b>1. Keep the soil moist:</b> Trees that are well-watered before cold weather hits are less likely to experience damage from freezing. Water trees deeply before the ground freezes to ensure the soil stays moist.\n\n</br>
<br><b>2. Mulch around the base of the tree:</b> Applying a layer of mulch around the base of the tree helps to insulate the roots and protect them from the cold. Use 2-3 inches of organic mulch, such as shredded leaves or wood chips, but avoid piling it up against the trunk of the tree.\n\n</br>
<br><b>3. Wrap the trunk:</b> Wrapping the trunk of young trees with burlap or other insulating material can help to protect the bark from extreme temperatures. This is especially important for thin-barked trees like maple or fruit trees.\n\n</br>
<br><b>4. Prune damaged or dead branches:</b> Remove any damaged or dead branches before the cold weather hits. These branches are more likely to break or fall off in extreme weather and can damage the tree.\n\n</br>
<br><b>5. Provide shelter:</b> If possible, provide shelter for your trees from the wind and cold. This can include erecting windbreaks or using burlap to create a screen around the tree.\n\n</br>
By taking these preventative measures, you can protect your trees from damage caused by cold weather and reduce the risk of them exploding. Remember to monitor your trees regularly throughout the winter and take action if you notice any signs of damage or stress.
    </string>

    <string name="birdssun">Birds Eating Sunflower Leaves In The Garden</string>
    <string name="description_birdssun">If birds are eating the leaves of your sunflower plants, there are a few steps you can take to deter them:\n\n
        <br><b>1. Use bird netting:</b> Covering your sunflower plants with bird netting can prevent birds from getting to the leaves. Make sure the netting is securely anchored to the ground to prevent birds from getting underneath it.\n\n</br>
<br><b>2. Provide alternative food sources:</b> Birds may be eating your sunflower leaves because they are hungry. Try providing them with alternative food sources, such as bird feeders or bird baths, to distract them from your sunflowers.\n\n</br>
<br><b>3. Scare tactics:</b> Birds are easily frightened by loud noises or sudden movements. Try hanging reflective tape or old CDs around your garden, or use a scarecrow or owl decoy to scare them away.\n\n</br>
<br><b>4. Use natural repellents:</b> Some natural repellents can be effective in deterring birds. For example, spraying a mixture of water and cayenne pepper on the leaves of your sunflower plants can make them less appealing to birds.\n\n</br>
<br><b>5. Plant extra sunflowers:</b> If you have enough space in your garden, planting extra sunflowers can help to spread out the damage caused by birds. This can also ensure that there are enough leaves for the birds to eat without damaging a single plant too much.\n\n</br>
Remember to be patient and persistent when trying to deter birds from eating your sunflower leaves. It may take a combination of methods to find what works best for your garden.
    </string>

    <string name="tuberrot">Tuber Rot Diseases</string>
    <string name="description_tuberrot">Tuber rot is a common disease that affects a variety of plants, including potatoes, sweet potatoes, and other tubers. Tuber rot diseases are caused by various fungi and bacteria that can infect tubers during the growing season or in storage. Here are some common tuber rot diseases and their symptoms:\n\n
<br><b>1. Fusarium dry rot:</b> This disease is caused by the fungus Fusarium spp. and is characterized by sunken, brown lesions on the tubers. The flesh inside the tuber is dry and powdery, and may have a musty smell.\n\n</br>
<br><b>2. Black scurf:</b> This disease is caused by the fungus Rhizoctonia solani and is characterized by black, irregular-shaped lesions on the surface of the tubers. The fungus may also form a web-like growth on the surface of the tubers.\n\n</br>
<br><b>3. Silver scurf:</b> This disease is caused by the fungus Helminthosporium solani and is characterized by a silver-gray, scaly appearance on the surface of the tubers. The flesh inside the tuber is not affected.\n\n</br>
<br><b>4. Soft rot:</b> This disease is caused by several bacteria, including Erwinia carotovora and Pectobacterium spp. and is characterized by soft, wet, and foul-smelling lesions on the tubers.\n\n</br>
To prevent tuber rot diseases, it is important to practice good crop management practices, such as crop rotation, maintaining soil moisture levels, and avoiding overcrowding. Additionally, it is important to store tubers in a cool, dry place to prevent the growth of fungi and bacteria. If you do notice signs of tuber rot in your crops, it is important to remove and discard affected plants and tubers to prevent the spread of the disease.
    </string>

    <string name="chicken">How To Use Fresh Chicken Manure In The Garden</string>
    <string name="description_chicken">Fresh chicken manure is a valuable source of nutrients for your garden, but it can also be very high in nitrogen and can burn your plants if not used properly. Here are some tips for using fresh chicken manure in your garden:\n\n
<br><b>1. Compost it first:</b> Fresh chicken manure is high in nitrogen and can be too strong for your plants. Composting it first will help to break it down and create a balanced mix of nutrients. Add some brown materials, such as dry leaves or straw, to the manure to balance out the high nitrogen content. Composting also helps to reduce the risk of pathogens in the manure.\n\n</br>
<br><b>2. Apply it in the fall:</b> Apply fresh chicken manure in the fall so that it has time to decompose before you plant in the spring. This will give the nutrients time to break down and be absorbed by the soil.\n\n</br>
<br><b>3. Mix it into the soil:</b> Mix the composted chicken manure into the soil before planting. This will help to distribute the nutrients evenly and prevent burning.\n\n</br>
<br><b>4. Use it sparingly:</b> Use chicken manure sparingly in your garden, especially if you have young or delicate plants. A little goes a long way and too much can burn your plants. Start with a small amount and see how your plants respond before adding more.\n\n</br>
<br><b>5. Don\'t use it on edible crops:</b> Avoid using fresh chicken manure on edible crops that are close to harvest time. The risk of contamination with pathogens is higher with fresh manure, so it\'s best to avoid using it on crops that you will be consuming soon.\n\n</br>
By following these tips, you can use fresh chicken manure in your garden without risking harm to your plants or contamination to your crops. Composting it first and using it sparingly will ensure that you get the benefits of this valuable resource without any negative side effects.
    </string>

    <string name="rose">How to Plant, Grow, and Care for Rose</string>
    <string name="description_rose">Roses are a classic and beloved flower that can be planted and grown in many climates. Here are some steps to plant, grow, and care for roses:\n\n
<br><b>1. Choose a suitable location:</b> Roses prefer full sun and well-draining soil. It is best to plant them in a location that gets at least 6 hours of sunlight per day.\n\n</br>
<br><b>2. Plant the Roses:</b> Dig a hole that is wider and deeper than the root ball of the rose bush. Place the rose bush in the hole, making sure that the root ball is level with the soil. Fill in the hole with soil and tamp it down gently to remove any air pockets.\n\n</br>
<br><b>3. Water the Roses:</b> Water the rose bush deeply once or twice a week, depending on the weather conditions. Be sure to water the plant at the base, not on the leaves, to prevent disease.\n\n</br>
<br><b>4. Fertilize the Roses:</b> Roses benefit from regular fertilization. Use a balanced fertilizer formulated specifically for roses and apply it according to the manufacturer\'s instructions.\n\n</br>
<br><b>5. Prune the Roses:</b> Prune the rose bush in late winter or early spring to remove any dead or damaged wood and to shape the plant. Remove any branches that cross or rub against each other.\n\n</br>
<br><b>6. Protect the Roses:</b> Roses can be damaged by pests like aphids, spider mites, and Japanese beetles. Use organic insecticides if necessary to manage these pests.\n\n</br>
<br><b>7. Harvest the Roses:</b> Enjoy the beautiful blooms of your rose bushes throughout the growing season. Cut the flowers with a sharp pair of pruning shears, making a clean cut just above a set of leaves.\n\n</br>
By following these steps, you can grow healthy and beautiful rose bushes that will bring joy to your garden for years to come.
    </string>

    <string name="todoagave">TODO</string>
    <string name="annual_plants">ANNUAL PLANTS</string>
    <string name="compost_basics">COMPOST BASICS</string>
    <string name="bee_garden">BEE GARDEN</string>
    <string name="todobee">TODO</string>


    <string-array name="Topics">
        <item>Select Topic</item>
        <item>Garden Categories</item>
        <item>Compost</item>
        <item>Problems</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>